made-in-china.com 2006-12-24

# Privacy Policy | Made-in-China.com

### Privacy Policy

Made-in-China.com makes a firm commitment to protect your privacy. The following policy will provide details of how your personal information is treated. This policy may be subject to change without notice, so please check back periodically. 

  * Why does Made-in-China.com collect your personal information?
  * What personal information is collected? 
  * Does Made-in-China.com collect other forms of information about its users?
  * How may your personal information be treated?
  * With whom may your information be shared?
  * What is our responsibility to ensure your privacy?
  * What can you do to protect your personal information?
  * How to contact us on further inquiry about our privacy policy?

##### Why does Made-in-China.com collect your personal information?

When you register as a Made-in-China.com member we collect all the information you enter. This includes your contact details, company name, address and etc. Membership statistics are derived from members' registration information, however no specific member is named or referred to in the resultant statistical reports. Statistics are generally used to classify our members by, for example, industry and country. This information may be used to target our registered members for new services and promotions. Your e-mail address may be used to contact you regarding new services and products in which you may be interested.

By knowing a little about you, Made-in-China.com is able to provide you with more relevant content and a higher level of customer service.

top

##### What personal information is collected?

We collect all the information that you manually enter during registration or update of your company profile. Please refer to your company profile or registration page to view all the information that is collected. You may edit your company and personal information at any time by clicking on Company Info from within the Virtual Office menu.

top

##### Does Made-in-China.com collect other information about its users?

In addition to the use of Profile Information to operate the site, Made-in-China.com also gathers anonymous information, which may be used by Made-in-China.com or shared with its advertisers. This information does not personally identify you. This information is primarily collected through "traffic data" and may entail the use of "Cookies", "IP addresses" or other numeric codes used to identify a computer. In order to login to the Made-in-China.com site, your browser must be configured to accept cookies.

top

##### How may your personal information be treated?

Made-in-China.com does not disclose your Profile Information to any third parties, unless acting under the belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Made-in-China.com; (3) enforce the Made-in-China.com Terms & Conditions; or (4) act to protect the interests of its members or others. Your Company Profile Information collected by Made-in-China.com is stored in secure operating environments that are only accessible to authorized Focus Technology Co., Ltd employees. 

Based on the information provided to us during registration, Made-in-China.com conducts research regarding users' demographics, industry and geographic location. This research is completed in order to better understand and serve our users. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. Made-in-China.com maintains the right to share this aggregated data with advertisers or business partners as required.

top

##### With whom may your information be shared?

Made-in-China.com will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances. Made-in-China.com may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain and improve our services.

top

##### What is our responsibility to ensure your privacy?

Once we receive your personal information, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems and will not share it with any third parties. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Made-in-China.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk.

top

##### What can you do to protect your personal information?

Your Made-in-China.com Account Information and Made-in-China.com Member Profile are password-protected so that other Made-in-China.com members will not have the ability to edit or delete this personal information. Please note that any password protection system may be vulnerable to computer "hackers", and therefore Made-in-China.com cannot 100% guarantee the protection of your personal information from malicious third parties. You may edit your Account and Profile Information at any time by using your Made-in-China.com ID and password. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone.

The information that you provide when posting an item for trade or when making an offer is posted in a public area, accessible to all users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

top

##### How to contact us on further inquiry about our privacy policy?

You may click here to contact us.

top
